Soheil Zarrinpour

Bandar-e Anzali, Gilan Province, Iran



parhamzarrin264@gmail.com



09035653125



linkedin.com/in/soheil-zarrinpour

Summary

My name is Sohail Zarinpour.

I am a bit quiet, so emotional, honest, intelligent, committed and introverted person.

After getting my diploma, I abandoned my academic studies and started learning about programming, and I have been practicing, learning, and doing projects for more than five years.

Currently, I am fluent in JavaScript, Angular, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Materialize, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, jQuery responsive design and meny more.

Experience



Frontend Developer

Self-employed

May 2019 - Present (3 years 8 months +)



Frontend Developer

Tose'e System Tavana Mar 2019 - Sep 2019 (7 months)

Education



ferdosi high school

High School Diploma, experimental diploma Sep 2012 - Jun 2013

Licenses & Certifications



HTML/CSS - TestDome

www.testdome.com/certificates/c01b31465dd44be595138d155061e3c9



Web Developer - TestDome

www.testdome.com/certificates/2977c6eb7ad042e08866b915ca0edd7e

Skills

JavaScript • CSS 3 • SCSS • HTML5 • ¡Query • Angular • Angular Material • PHP • MySQL • Materialize CSS